<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>My Blogs</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/</link><description>Recent content on My Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:29:28 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Build Portfolio Website with Hugo</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:29:28 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/hugo/</guid><description>A personal webpage is a perfect place to let the world know about you and showcase your past accomplishments. Put your resume, your projects, your blogs in with a personalized theme which makes people know you have a great taste: all-in-one! ItΓÇÖs your portfolio displayed online, a small yet cool project you can do with not much effort, why not?
With Github Pages, we can host a personal webpage without bothering about finding a domain name, and with Hugo, we have a variety of themes to choose from.</description></item><item><title>SCRCPY : Screen Mirroring</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/scrcpy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 19:51:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/scrcpy/</guid><description>Sometimes you need to mirror your mobile screen in to your desktop. For that you may have to install some heavy softwares. But you can just connect your mobile phone to your desktop and easily can mirror your phone and you can also control your mobile phone with your desktop machine. Because the project is open source on github this application is actively made updates to increase the security. Download the package from this link</description></item><item><title>Create Beautiful Readme without Coding</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/first/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 19:46:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/first/</guid><description>Github readme profile is very good way to present yourself. It is written in Markdown Language. But to make it very easy there is open source website to generate readme code by just filling the form .
To make use this open source website Click here Developed BY - rahuldkjain
Some Readme Made using this website :
rahuldkjain Varshithvhegde</description></item></channel></rss>