<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on My Blogs</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on My Blogs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 14:01:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awesome Web Projects Ideas You Can put it on your Resume</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/awesome_web_projects/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 14:01:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/awesome_web_projects/</guid><description>Introduction This is a list of awesome web projects that I have created. These projects can also be put on your resume. I have created this list to help you decide which projects you can put on your resume.
Hosting If we are talking about web projects, it is important to know how to host your web project. Because you cannot show your web project to the world without hosting it.</description></item><item><title>Create Your Own Live Web Editor using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/htmleditor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 20:52:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/htmleditor/</guid><description>Introduction In this tutorial, we will be creating a live web editor. This is a web application that allows you to write HTML, CSS, and JavaScript code and see the results in real time. This is a great tool for learning web development and for testing out code snippets. We will be using the iframe element to display the results. The iframe element is used to embed another document within the current HTML document.</description></item><item><title>Create an Android App with SignUp And SignIn using Firebase</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/signin_signup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 21:37:38 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/signin_signup/</guid><description>PREREQUISITE: Installation of Android Studio. Must be aware of Java language. Basic concepts of android. What is firebase? Firebase is Google&amp;rsquo;s mobile development platform. It provides you the platform to quickly and high-quality app with a better user base. There are multiple complementary features in firebase you can use according to your known needs.
The main need to connect firebase with the android studio is that the Google repository version is equal to or greater than 26.</description></item><item><title>Build Portfolio Website with Hugo</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 20:29:28 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/hugo/</guid><description>A personal webpage is a perfect place to let the world know about you and showcase your past accomplishments. Put your resume, your projects, your blogs in with a personalized theme which makes people know you have a great taste: all-in-one! It’s your portfolio displayed online, a small yet cool project you can do with not much effort, why not?
With Github Pages, we can host a personal webpage without bothering about finding a domain name, and with Hugo, we have a variety of themes to choose from.</description></item><item><title>SCRCPY : Screen Mirroring</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/scrcpy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 19:51:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/scrcpy/</guid><description>Sometimes you need to mirror your mobile screen in to your desktop. For that you may have to install some heavy softwares. But you can just connect your mobile phone to your desktop and easily can mirror your phone and you can also control your mobile phone with your desktop machine. Because the project is open source on github this application is actively made updates to increase the security. Download the package from this link</description></item><item><title>Create Beautiful Readme without Coding</title><link>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/first/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 19:46:59 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://symphonious-puffpuff-d7704c.netlify.app/posts/first/</guid><description>Github readme profile is very good way to present yourself. It is written in Markdown Language. But to make it very easy there is open source website to generate readme code by just filling the form .
To make use this open source website Click here Developed BY - rahuldkjain
Some Readme Made using this website :
rahuldkjain Varshithvhegde</description></item></channel></rss>